くっ
Crap.
We can't do anything like this.
くそう！　これじゃ手も足もでねえ
What should we do? Should we charge in?
どうする？　一気に突っ込んでみるか？
Hey, say something! I'm going already.
おい！　なんとか言え！
もう行っちゃうぞ 俺！
All right...
分かりました　右から回り込みましょう
Let's go around from the right.
Okay, left it is then!
ＯＫ 分かった　左だな
The right?!
Think about the direction the wind is blowing.
右？
風向きを考えてください
In theory, it would be better to go from the right.
この状況
セオリーから言ったら右ですよ
"Theory"? Whatever!
何がセオリーだよ
My instinct is telling me to go left. Let's go.
俺の勘が言ってる
左だ　行くぞ
No, go right.
いや 右です
くっ
It doesn't matter which way we go!
もうどっちでもいいだろ！
Then let's go right.
Left!
なら右で
左だ
Hey, Lil' Bunny, you should follow your elders' example.
おいバニーちゃんよ
先輩の意見にはな 素直に従ったほうが
Huh? What?
ん？
えっ？
gokigen yo doukashitan darou?
How are you? Is something wrong?
ごきげんよう どうかしたんだろ？
kao wo mireba isshun de wakaru yo
I can tell just by looking at you.
顔を見れば一瞬でわかるよ
senrigan senrigan? messou nai desu
Am I psychic? Of course not.
千里眼千里眼？
めっそうないです
taikutsu GIRL megumaretai no kai
Bored girl, do you want to find happiness?
退屈ガール 恵まれたいのかい
hantei wa shingi no renzoku de
Let's think it through and decide.
判定は審議の連続で
VENUS SUSTAIN
Venus Sustain.
ヴィーナスサステイン
odoru machinami
The city dances.
踊る街並み
PERFECTLY EUPHORIA
Perfectly, Euphoria!
Perfectly Euphoria！
nandemo nai youna kotoba de naitari suru shi
I end up crying over the smallest things.
何でもないような
言葉で泣いたりするし
hora bokutachi nante
Come on, our
ほら 僕達なんて
zentei no nai
temporary passion
juubun tekido ni
lives are
十分適度に
zentei no nai
a temporary passion
DRAMATIC sa
reasonably dramatic.
ドラマチックさ
saikou no wa
the best passion
karuku SUPER STAR
We're almost like super stars!
軽くスーパースター
ORION wo nazoru konna fukai yoru
Looking up at Orion late at night.
オリオンをなぞる こんな深い夜
tsunagaretai hanasaretai
I want to connect. I want to be free.
つながりたい 離されたい
tsumari hanshinhangi acchi kocchi
Basically, I'm not sure and can't decide.
つまり半信半疑あっちこっち
shin mirai wo negau kuuzenzetsugo no
I pray for a new future. The greatest one yet.
新未来を願う 空前絶後の
kotoba ga moshi, moshi tsumugeru nara jikan ga tomaru yo
If I could spin words, time would stop.
言葉がもし もし紡げるなら
時間が止まるよ
koko de owaru hazu ga nai no ni
"There's no way it can end here."
｢ココデオワルハズガナイノニ｣
I've told you over and over...
だから何度も言ったのに
Please stop calling me "Bunny"!
いい加減
バニーって呼ぶのやめてください
Huh?
あ？
Haven't you had enough already?
もういいでしょう
There's no point in continuing this silly game.
こんな茶番
これ以上続けても意味がない
This proves it.
これで分かりましたよ
Your reliance on instinct makes it impossible
あなたみたいに
勘に頼るようなやり方じゃ
for me to team up with you.
やっぱり僕とは組めない
ふんっ
For your information, simulations aren't—
俺はそもそも
シミュレーションなんて…
シミュレーションなんて嫌いなんです
Simulations aren't my thing.
I can't go all out unless it's the real thing.
実践じゃないと本気になれませんから
ちっ
ふう
ん？
Oh, please don't mind us! Just act natural!
ああ どうぞどうぞ
こっちはお構いなく
自然体で
あ…
Acting so cocky...
偉そうに　何が実戦じゃないとだ
What does he mean,
he can't go all out unless it's the real thing?
はあ…　分かる？
Don't you get it?
Our selling point is the fact that we have a team.
うちはコンビが売りなんですよ
And yet, your teamwork is terrible. Do you know why?
なのに 全然意気があってない
なぜかな？
ったく これじゃなんのために
君を雇ったか 分かりませんね
Jeez, I don't know why I bothered to hire you, Mr. Kotetsu.
虎徹君
What? It's my fault?
なっ！　俺のせい？
Then I'm leaving.
じゃ 僕帰ります
Hey! You...
おい！
Never mind him!
彼はいいの！
Thanks to Barnaby, our stock prices are skyrocketing.
今や バーナビーのおかげで
うちの株価は天井知らず
Listen. People are expecting a lot from you two.
いいですか？
期待されているんです　君たちは
This is a crucial time, got it?
大事な時期なの　今
Okay...
はあ…
君が若い彼を引っ張っていかないで
どうするんだ？
He's young, so why don't you try to lead him?
キャリアだけで言えば
君のほうが上なんだし
You've been doing this for much longer, after all.
そりゃそうですが
That's true, but...
例えば…
For example...
ほら シミュレーションで
二人の連携を高めるとか
How about working to improve your team coordination
through a training simulation, or something like that?
方法はあるでしょ？
シミュレーション？
A simulation?
What?
何？
いや 俺
シミュレーションて苦手なんです
Well... I don't really like simulations.
緊張感がなくて
There's no tension. I prefer the real thing.
やっぱ実戦じゃないと
嫌なら辞めてもらっても
構わないんですよ？
If you don't like it, you can quit.
はあ…
Making such an elaborate facility...
手の込んだものを作りやがって
What if I catch a cold?
風邪ひいたらどうすんだよ！
ワイルドタイガー ちょっといい？
Wild Tiger, do you have a moment?
今はミスター鏑木と
呼んだほうが良かったかしら？
Or should I refer to you as Mr. Kaburagi right now?
バーナビー？
Barnaby?
He's a rival, but as a fellow Hero who defends the same city,
ライバルだが俺はあいつに
期待しているよ
同じ街を守る ヒーローとしてな
I have high hopes for him!
He's a cute kid.
キュートな子ね
He's the perfect new Hero.
ニューヒーローとしては
申し分ないんじゃない？
He's got a pretty face,
綺麗な顔だし
女の子にも人気あるかもね
so he's got to be popular with the ladies too.
女の子にも…
Especially with the ladies...
I sense something from him.
彼は 何かを感じさせてくれる
だから私は彼に言いたい
So I'd like to tell him, "Thanks. And thanks again."
ありがとう
そしてありがとうと
ん…　特にない
I've got nothing.
ちょっとストップ！
Hold on, stop right there.
What do you mean you've got nothing?
特にないってどういうこと？
You're his partner, aren't you?
あなた彼のパートナーでしょ？
What is it? Do you want to ruin my show?
何？　私の企画ぶち壊したいの？
I just don't have anything to say. I can't help it.
ないもんはないんだから
仕方ないだろ？
You're not a child. Don't you have anything better to say?
子供じゃないんだから
もっとマシなコメントあんでしょ？
俺よりスカイハイに言えよ！
なんだよ！
Tell that to Sky High!
え？
Huh?
ありがとう
そして ありがとうって？
"Thanks. And thanks again"? What's that about?
いいのよ　彼はあれで
There's nothing wrong with him saying that.
Huh?
え？
天然が持ち味なんだから
That goofiness is his strong point!
That's not fair!
ずりいぞ！
Okay. I'll come up with the lines, and you'll repeat it.
ＯＫ 私が考えるから
そのまま言いなさい
はあ？
Huh?
あなたはそれを読んで
Just read it out loud.
ん？　ふっ
Are you following me home too?
もしかして家の中もですか？
Yes.
ええ なんせバーナビーさんの
密着ドキュメントですから
This is an in-depth documentary, after all!
あんまり面白みのない部屋で
Sorry my room isn't very interesting.
申し訳ないんですけど
It's all right!
いえいえ ファンはね
The fans want to see how you spend
こういうプライベートな部分を
一番見たいんですよ
your personal time more than anything.
あ…
What is it?
何か？
I understand. I'm also a single man.
分かりますよ〜
私も同じ独身男ですから
Excuse me?
は？
I'll make sure to cut out scenes
万一 イメージ崩すような事があっても
カットします
that might ruin your public image.
はあ…
Okay...
In return, let me know if there are any sites you recommend.
そのかわり お勧めのサイトあったら
こっそり教えてくださいよ？
ふっ
本日 シュテルンメダイユ地区に
新たに建設された
Today, in the Stern Medaille Area, a ceremony was held to
フォートレスタワービルの
完成記念式典が行われました
commemorate the completion of the Fortress Tower Building.
A statue of Legend, the first Hero, has been placed
なお 平和の象徴として
ビルのエントランスには
at the entrance of the building as a symbol of peace.
初代ヒーロー
レジェンドの像が飾られ
Mr. Albert Maverick was present at its unveiling.
その除幕式に
アルバート・マーベリック氏が
立ち会いました
We hope that Fortress Tower Building
このフォートレスタワービルが
シュテルンビルトの新しい名所
will become Stern Bild's new landmark,
そして 新たな平和のシンボルと
なってくれることを願います
as well as its new symbol of peace.
さあ行こう
It's time to go.
It's all right. You're not alone anymore.
大丈夫
君はもう一人じゃない
I'm still alone, sir...
俺は未だに一人ですよ
Hey, Lil' Bunny.
よう バニーちゃん
ん？
Umm... Want to go out?
えっと…
ちょっと街にでも繰り出さないか？
What's this all about? It's creepy.
なんですか 急に？
気持ちの悪い
I don't know, okay?!
知らねえよ
Huh?
何その大根芝居！
What kind of horrible acting was that?!
And his name is Barnaby, not Lil' Bunny.
あとバニーちゃんじゃなくて
バーナビー！
変なあだ名つけないで！
Don't give him strange nicknames!
It's not a big deal.
いいだろう？
今日は あなたがパートナーの
バーナビーを誘って街に繰り出す
Today, you're going to invite your partner, Barnaby,
to a day out on the town.
That's the scenario. Do it properly.
そういう演出なんだから
きちんとやって！
I'm not an actor!
俺は役者じゃねえんだよ
Listen. This is all business.
いい？　これはビジネスなの
ふっ
So what should I do?
で 僕はどうすれば？
Just act the way you usually do.
いつも通りに過ごしていただければ
The way I usually do? Got it.
いつも通り…　分かりました
ふう
Yeah, this is the way things usually are, but...
確かにいつもこうだけど
うわあ
Barnaby!
バーナビー
Here you go.
Wow!
I'm next!
やっぱ絵になるわね
We're getting a great picture here. On the other hand...
それに比べて…
What do you mean, you don't want it?!
いらねえってどういうことだよ
I'm giving it to you for free!
おじさん
タダでやるって言ってんだぞ？
だって それカッコよくないんだもん
That's because that one's not cool.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
おい レアだぞこれ！
Hey!
I got one from Barnaby too.
This one's rare!
All right!
Don't come begging me for it later on!
あとでくれって言っても やんないぞ
Hey...
おいって…
Here we go.
いきま〜す
Huh?!
ええ？　何この人？
What's with this person?!
なんなんですか？
You ruined it!
あいつもよくやるよな？
He sure does a good job putting up with all of this...
Oh yeah, and him too...
あいつもそうだけど
Hey... Don't you think we've done enough?
なあ？　もう十分だろ？
ＯＫ そろそろ日も暮れてきたし
移動しましょう
Okay. The sun is going down, so let's get moving.
We're doing more?!
まだあんのかよ！
Next up is Fortress Tower Building.
次は フォートレスタワービル
ん？
My superiors want me to give
新名所のＰＲも兼ねろって
上からのお達しなの
their new landmark some publicity.
So this is it...
これか！
Let's get going.
さっさと行くわよ
ああ…
なあ？　もっとこれ撮ったほうが
いいんじゃない？
Hey, shouldn't you be filming this?
This place needs the publicity, right?
ＰＲなんだろ？
ん？
Is it malfunctioning?
故障かしら？
Hey...
おい
Can we get on?
乗っていいのか？
ああ 修理は終わったよ
Yeah. I just finished fixing it.
Fixing it? This place was just completed.
修理？
できたばっかだろ ここ？
It's nothing. I was just oiling the cables.
ああ なんてことないよ
ケーブルに油を注したぐらいだ
Are you getting in or not?
ねえ 乗るの？　乗らないの？
げっ
Oh... Do I have to get in?
あ 乗らなくてもいいのか
Just get in!
さっさと乗って
Isn't that Barnaby?
あれバーナビーじゃない？
かっこいい
He's so cool!
キャー
Don't you get tired of doing that?
お前 そういうの疲れない？
Doing what?
何がですか？
Umm...
あの…
握手してもらってもいいですか？
May I shake your hand?
ええ 構いませんよ
Sure. I don't mind.
わあ！　ありがとうございます
Thank you very much!
そういうのだよ
That sort of stuff.
別に
Not really. It's all part of our job.
すべて仕事ですから
By the way, sir...
ねえ 先輩
You're creeping me out now...
なんだよ きもい
What's that?
あれは何ですか？
Figure it out your—
そんなもん てめえで し…
Which you don't have to do. What are you looking at?
調べることはない
どれだい？
あれです
That.
That's... a building.
あれは…　ビルってやつだ
じゃあ あっちのは？
Then... what's that?
That's also a building.
あれもビルだな
Also, the thing next to it is a building
ついでに言うと
その隣の建物がビルで
and the thing in front of it is also a building.
その手前に建つ建物もビル
Well... all the building-like structures
ま こっから見える
ビル的な建物は 全部ビルだ
you can see here are buildings.
真面目にやんなさいよ！
Be serious!
いや 俺だってよく知らねえんだよ
I really don't know what they're called.
あっ
Attention, all visitors...
お客様にお知らせ致します
ただ今
館内で非常警報が発生致しました
An alarm has just been set off in the building.
何？
What's going on?
係員の指示に従って
速やかに行動してください
Please follow the staff's instructions and move quickly.
Please evacuate!
避難してください！
Everyone! Please evacuate right away.
皆さんすぐ避難してください！
I repeat...
どした　火事でもあったか？
What's wrong? ls there a fire?
Oh well...
いえ その…
Barnaby and Wild Tiger.
バーナビーとワイルドタイガー
え？
They're both Heroes.
二人ともヒーローよ
ああ
I see...
実は爆弾を仕掛けたという
脅迫電話がありまして
To tell you the truth, we had a bomb threat.
えっ
Where's the bomb?
場所は？
Well, we have no idea where it is.
それが具体的な場所などは 一切…
It might be a prank, but...
いたずらだとは思うんですが…
Did the culprit make any demands?
犯人側から何か要求は？
Not really.
そういったことも特には…
He's doing it for fun, huh?
愉快犯だ
I was just oiling the cables.
ケーブルに油を注したぐらいだ
あっ
悪い ここを頼むわ
Sorry. Take care of things here.
ちょっと！　どこ行くの？
Hey, where are you going?
I'll be right back!
すぐ戻る！
A bomb?
あっ
It's all right, everyone. It's just a stupid joke.
大丈夫ですよ 皆さん
たちの悪いいたずらです
To be safe, though, please evacuate.
ですが 念のため避難してください
Think of this as an evacuation exercise.
避難訓練だと思って
あっ
You're joking, right?
おいおい
こんなもん ビルごと吹っ飛んじまうぞ
That thing could blow up this entire building!
Everyone, stay calm.
皆さん 焦らなくて大丈夫ですから
Everything will be just fine.
順番に ゆっくり降りてください
Please go down slowly, one at a time!
The Hero saving people during his personal time...
ヒーローのプライベートでの救出劇
We don't get many chances to film this.
こんな絵はめったに撮れないわ
Ms. Agnes...
アニエスさん
Shouldn't we start evacuating too?
そろそろ我々も避難したほうが
Are you crazy?! You call yourself a member of the media
何言ってんの？
それでもあなたテレビマン？
with that kind of attitude?
How much time do we have left?
残り時間は？
あったのね？
So there was a bomb.
Let's go.
行こう
くっ
Listen. We're going to follow
いい？　このまま二人を追うから
and stick to those two as long as we can!
ギリギリまで粘るわよ
What are you just standing there for?!
何ぐずぐずしてんの？
You guys should also evacuate.
あんたらも今すぐ避難するんだ
Huh? You've got to be kidding me.
はあ？　ふざけないで
If I let an opportunity as great as this slip away, I'd be—
こんなおいしい場面
みすみす逃げ出したら一生…
Who's the one kidding around?!
ふざけてんのはどっちだよ！
I don't mind that you think of this as a show.
おたくらは
ショーのつもりかもしれないし
別にそれはそれで構わない
But not in our current situation.
ただし 現場となると話は別だ
We Heroes have a duty
俺たちヒーローには
常に市民を守る義務がある
to protect the citizens of this city at all times.
あんたたちも 俺が守る
And you guys are no exception.
He was kind of cool, wasn't he?
あいつ
ちょっとかっこよかったっスね
Him? Yeah, right.
はあ？　どこが！
But we have a job to do...
けど 私たちにだって仕事が…
Don't worry. He'll be running the camera for you.
大丈夫ですよ
そのカメラは彼が回しますから
え？
What?!
ふん！
Bring the broadcasting van! I'll be directing personally.
すぐ中継車をまわして！
私が直接指示する！
The Fortress Tower Building received
本日19時15分
フォートレスタワービル内において
爆弾が仕掛けられたという事件が発生
a bomb threat at 7:15 p.m. today!
The staff and visitors are rushing to evacuate.
従業員 客の全員が
避難する騒ぎとなりました
Heroes who made it to the scene appear
なお 現在は駆けつけた
ヒーローたちの活躍によって
従業員 客 ともに避難はすべて
無事完了したもようです
to have evacuated all of the visitors and staff!
We still do not know what
しかし まだ犯人の狙い 要求などは
一切不明のもよう
the culprit's objectives and demands are.
完成間もないビルに
突然降って沸いた この爆弾騒ぎ
This building was just completed
and there's already been a bomb scare.
Is there really a bomb? Or is this just a prank?
果たして爆弾は本当にあるのか
それともただのいたずらなのか
さあ パーティースタートよ
Now let the party begin.
We can only wait as things progress.
Let's see if they can really pull this off.
ホントに大丈夫なのかしら？
Now then, what should we do, Bunny?
さあ どうする バニー？
Shall we at least smile for the camera?
とりあえずカメラに笑って見せるか？
How did you know that it was here?
どうして
ここにあるって分かったんですか？
It's strange for a new elevator to be malfunctioning.
できたばっかのエレベーターが
いきなり故障ってのもおかしいだろ？
Is that all?
それだけで？
You saw that worker too, right?
お前も見たろ？
あの作業員
He looked too clean to have been working with the cables.
ケーブルいじったにしちゃ
綺麗すぎるんだよ
His clothes and gloves too.
服も手袋もよ
I see. That's pretty good, for you.
なるほど　あなたにしては上出来ですね
Why the condescending tone?!
なんで上から目線なんだよ！
Anyway, what are you doing?
つうか 何やってんだ？
You probably rushed here without much thought, didn't you?
どうせたいした考えもなしに
勢いだけでここにきたんでしょ？
いひっ
I've learned how to deal with bombs.
爆弾処理なら
以前 習得しましたから
You can do that?
お前さん
そんなことまでできちゃうわけ？
A Hero should be able to handle any situation.
あらゆる出来事に対処できてこその
ヒーローですよ
Well, yeah. Ideally, that's the case, but...
まあ あの…
理想はそうだけど
I get it now. Well, let's see what you can do.
なるほどね　まっ とりあえず
お手並み拝見させていただきますよ
What are you doing?
何してるんですか？
What am I doing? I don't have anything to do, so I'm resting.
何ってやることないから寝てんだよ
悪いか？
Do you have a problem with that?
If that's the case, then evacuate. I'll handle this by myself.
だったら避難してください
僕一人でなんとかしますから
You idiot.
ばぁか 相棒残して一人で逃げるほど
落ちぶれちゃいねえよ
I'm not so heartless that I'd escape without my partner.
What is it?
なんだよ？
Nothing... As always, your thinking is old-fashioned.
いや 相変わらず古臭いんですよ
考え方が
Shut up!
うるせえ！
Oh, but let me make this clear.
あっ でもいいか？
別に俺はお前を信じたわけじゃねえぞ？
This doesn't mean I've come to trust you or anything.
It's only because I have my pride as a Hero, and...
俺にもヒーローとしての
意地とか プライドってもんが…
That's fine and all, but could you keep quiet for a bit?
いるのは勝手ですが
少し黙っててもらえます？
はいはい 悪かったよ
Fine, fine, sorry.
According to the information we have,
情報によりますと
なんと ビルに偶然居合わせた
Barnaby and Wild Tiger happened to be in the area
バーナビーとワイルドタイガーの
二人のヒーローが
and are dealing with the bomb!
爆弾の処理に
あたっているとのことです
How do they feel about dealing
ヒーロースーツもない彼らは
一体 どんな心境で
with the bomb without their Hero suits?!
爆弾と向き合っているのでしょうか
They don't have much time left!
もう 残された時間の猶予はありません
The fate of this building has been left
今や このビルの命運は
アポロンメディアの
in the hands of Apollon Media's new duo!
It's a boring picture,
地味な絵だからあおっても
いまひとつ盛り上がらないんですよね
so there's nothing we can do to make it more exciting.
It would be nice if we could get a shot from inside.
せめて中の様子が
映せりゃいいんですけど
Tiger's the only one who saw the bomb, right?
結局 爆弾を見たのって
タイガーだけなんでしょ？
Is there really a bomb?
本当にあるんですかね？
案外 これを期に 人気者になろうとか
考えてるだけだったりして
This might just be his plan to boost his popularity.
Be quiet for a bit!
ちょっと黙って！
Don't die, Kotetsu.
死ぬんじゃねえぞ　虎徹
Hey, aren't you done yet?
おい まだかよ？
Hey, what's the progress like?
なあ どうなってんだよ？
We don't have time to escape anymore.
もう逃げてる暇もないぞ？
All right!
よし！
You did it?!
いったか？
I've dealt with the conductor, so now...
これで導線の処理は終わりました
あとは…
なんだよ？
What is it?
I just have to avoid the trap.
トラップを避けるだけです
What?
はあ？
There is a cable above and below the detonator.
雷管を挟んで
ケーブルが上下に２本
How wonderful.
なんとまあ ご丁寧に
どちらか正しいほうを切断したら
起爆装置は作動しなくなります
If I cut the right one, the bomb won't go off.
まどろっこしい言い方
してんじゃねえよ！
Just get to the point!
Choose the wrong one, and we'll be blown to bits! Is that it?
間違えたら俺たちゃ
木っ端微塵ってこったろ！
そういうことです
That's right.
Top or bottom... This is so cliché.
上か下か　く〜 お約束だな
So which one is it?
で？　どっちなんだよ？
もう時間ねえぞ
We don't have any time!
それが分かれば
とっくに切ってますよ！
If I knew which one, I would have cut it already!
上切れ 上！
Cut the top one!
根拠は？
Why?
じゃあ 下！
Then the bottom one!
勘で言わないでください
Don't rely on your instincts!
俺の勘は当たるんだよ！
My instinct is pretty accurate!
巻き添えはごめんです！
I don't want to get blown up!
Then what do your theories tell you is the right one?
セオリーとやらじゃ
どっちが正解なんだ？
だから それを今考えてるんです！
I'm thinking about that right now.
There's no point in hesitating!
迷ってても仕方ねえだろ！
あっ
上か 下
Top... or bottom...
Hey, go top!
おい！　上だ！
くっ
はっ
How did you know what I meant by "top"?
上って言った意味 何で分かった？
It was an instantaneous decision.
とっさの判断というか
There was nothing else I could do.
まあ ああするしかないでしょう
それって勘だろ？
Isn't that instinct?
Whatever the case,
どっちにしろ実践じゃないと
だめってこったな　お互い
neither of us does well unless we're in a real situation.
You're free to interpret it however you like.
好きに解釈していただいて結構です
ん？
I don't care for such feelings of camaraderie.
そういう仲間意識は 好きじゃないので
For a rabbit, you're not very cute.
ほんっとにお前かわいくねえな
うさぎのくせに
Excuse me?
はあ？
We can finally have a look at what happened at the scene.
ようやく現場の映像が届きました！
The top one is the only choice!
上しかないだろ！
Wild Tiger's mighty fists roar into action!
ワイルドタイガーの豪腕が唸る！
Followed by Barnaby's...
そしてバーナビーの強烈なキックが
炸裂！
explosive kick!
おおおおお！
They really let loose.
派手にやってくれたわね
まっ そのほうがありがたいんだけど
Well, I'm glad that they did.
So...
で この映像どうします？
What should we do with this footage?
Well, we can't air it!
流せるわけないでしょ
そんな映像
You don't think enough.
だいたいあなたは
詰めが甘いんですよ
Destroying the roof is too short-sighted.
天井破るなんて 短絡的すぎる
No matter how I think about it, kicking a bomb isn't right!
どう考えても
爆弾蹴るほうがおかしいだろ！
What if it had exploded?
爆発したらどうすんだ！
頭が固いな おじさんは
You're so hard-headed, old man.
なにい!
What?!
僕が消え 遠い未来で
boku ga kie tooi mirai de kaseki ni nattara
When I die and become a fossil in the far future,
化石になったら
人は僕に何を見るだろう
hito wa boku ni nani wo miru darou?
what will people see me as?
分析して 名を付けて
bunseki shite na wo tsukete kaidoku wo shitemo
They may try to analyze, name, and understand me,
解読をしても
愛した人は僕しか知らない
aishita hito wa boku shika shiranai
but only I will know the person I loved.
ハロー　生きること
HELLO ikiru koto
Hello, existence.
君の他に 君はできない
kimi no hoka ni kimi wa dekinai
Only you alone can live your life.
輝き続ける光った星から
kagayaki tsuzukeru hikatta hoshi kara
From the bright star that continues to shine,
輝き続け 光ったあの空から
kagayaki tsuzuke hikatta ano sora kara
from that bright sky that continues to shine.
僕らは何を感じられるだろう
bokura wa nani wo kanjirareru darou?
What can we feel from it?
奇跡は宇宙だけじゃないよ
kiseki wa uchuu dake janai yo
The universe isn't the only miracle.
輝き続ける光った星から
kagayaki tsuzukeru hikatta hoshi kara
From the bright star that continues to shine,
輝き続け 光ったあの空から
kagayaki tsuzuke hikatta ano sora kara
from that bright sky that continues to shine.
目を閉じたって 閉じきれないよ
me wo tojitatte tojikirenaiyo
You can try to shut your eyes, but you can't shut out your heart.
あの星さえ
ano hoshi sae motenakatta kokoro
It's something that even the stars did not possess.
持てなかった心
焼酎 ロックで
A shochu... On the rocks.
なあ どんなやつだったんだ？
Say...
What did the bomber look like?
爆弾犯
なんか 普通の悪そうなやつ
He looked like your average bad guy.
そうか
Ｃ９なんか持ち出しやがってよ
I see.
Bringing out a C9... What's wrong with him?
どうなってんだかな
Ｃ９てお前 最新爆弾だろ
A C9? That's the latest bomb out there!
なんでそんなものが
How did he get one of those?
ったく 嫌な世の中だよ
Jeez. What a terrible world this is.
バーナビーとはうまくやれてんのか？
So are you getting along with Barnaby?
さあな
Who knows?
えっ バーナビー君？
Umm... Barnaby? He's the best partner.
最高のパートナーですよ
こう見えて俺たち
結構似てるところがあるんです
We may not look it, but we have a lot in common!
ふっ
ん？
ただいまの演奏は
当店期待の新人シンガー
That song was by our new performer, Miss Karina Lyle.
カリーナ・ライルさんでした
ああっ
はあ？
Huh?
ども！　TIGER ＆ BUNNYの
何にでもマヨネーズをかけるほう
Hello! I'm Kotetsu, the member of "Tiger & Bunny"
虎徹です
who puts mayonnaise on everything!
おおぅ
歌ってるね　ブルーローズ
あら？　素顔でも歌ってる
Nice! Blue Rose is singing.
え？　ヒーロー辞めるって？
Huh? She's singing out of costume?
What? She's going to quit being a Hero?!
次回　TIGER ＆ BUNNY
Fear is ofte…　Fe…　え？
Next time on TIGER & BUNNY: